

Jeevadeepan Amuthurajan

SR. FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER / ASPIRING FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Profile

Passionate web developer with 10 years of experience in creating web user interfaces using Javascript, HTML and CSS. Professional experience in creating web UI components using React, Angular, Typescript and related web technologies. Strong desire for pixel perfect UI implementations using clean, reusable and testable code. An avid fan of functional programming paradigm. Aspiring full stack developer with a keen interest to learn new technologies.

Employment History

Senior Front end Web Developer, Morgan Stanley, New York City

DECEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

Developed Single page applications using React, Angular, Typescript and related Front end technologies for various business groups under Lending products and services team.

Javascript programmer, Ness Technologies/CDK Global, Seattle

SEPTEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2018

Developed javascript util libraries to handle internationalization (i18n) tasks.

Developed web user interfaces under GM professional services team for 'websites', a saas product.

UI Developer, Morgan Stanley India, Bengaluru

MARCH 2014 - MARCH 2016

Developed modular, reusable UI components for applications used by Fixed income business users using Angular js, Typescript, ExtJS.

UI Developer, Pramati Technologies, Hyderabad

JUNE 2012 - FEBRUARY 2014

Developed web User Interface for AJ Gallagher, Big machines and contributed to in-house projects socialbyway and Matisse.

UI Developer, Tata Consultancy Services, Chennai

NOVEMBER 2010 - JUNE 2012

Involved in UI development of centurylink web portal to enhance shopping order page and re-branding projects.

Education

Bachelors in Computer Science Engineering, Anna University, Chennai

AUGUST 2006 - MAY 2010

Details

7344310742 jeevacse89@gmail.com

Skills

JavaScript

React

HTML & CSS

Angular

Git

Node.js

Jest

Redux/Mobx

jQuery

babel

webpack / rollup

Jasmine/Mocha/Karma

GraphQL

Google Cloud Platform

Docker

NextJS